<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 22:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Front Matter CMS</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/front-matter-cms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 22:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/front-matter-cms/</guid>
      <description>A while ago I was talking about possibly using Ulysses as my Markdown writing tool of choice. I tried using it to write a few posts to this blog but I ran into several issues. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into them in detail but just summarize them by saying that Ulysses will edit the content of the YAML front matter in your files in such a way that is contrary to the YAML specifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Links page</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/creating-a-links-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 14:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/creating-a-links-page/</guid>
      <description>I joke with my friends that a programmer is a person who is a particular type of lazy. They will spend hours or even days on writing code or building a system so they never have to do a task twice. Regardless of the size of the task. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if this is a universal trait but it does describe how I often approach tasks that I know I will repeat again and again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/buildingwithhugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/buildingwithhugo/</guid>
      <description>This site is built using a static site generator called Hugo. Hugo is a command line tool written using the Go language that takes Markdown or HTML pages and builds a website using a theme you specify. The resulting site consists of static HTML pages and so it loads ridiculously quickly and the pages are much smaller than pages built with a CMS.
I am using a theme for the site based on the Poison theme which is itself based on another theme called Hyde.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
