<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ADHD on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/adhd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ADHD on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under the CC BY-NC-ND 4.0 license. https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:22:25 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/adhd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Smiling</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/smiling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:22:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/smiling/</guid>
      <description>There is an article making the rounds online, AI and the American Smile, that is a very interesting look at the social construction of the meaning of a smile. I found it rather interesting especially since my facial expressions have been a constant source of problems for me.
Doing a search for autism facial expressions leads to a wealth of articles and papers discussing the problems that people with spectrum disorders have in reading facial expressions and having their own moods misrepresented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moods</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/moods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 10:13:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/moods/</guid>
      <description>I have been creating a vault in Obsidian to contain some of my older bookmarks and links to pages for possible blog posts. It makes it easier to search them and I can also copy over the text from any webpages using the MarkDownload extension.
On a bit of a whim I added a daily notes page and a mood tracker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking languidly</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/breaking-languidly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/breaking-languidly/</guid>
      <description>The Tower Defence games should have been the first warning.
I truly love TD games, especially Core Defense, and have had since I saw Fieldrunners on the iPad. Fieldrunners was followed by Fieldrunners 2 which was even better than the original and which I have played to completion several times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Garden</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/secret-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/secret-garden/</guid>
      <description>The internet was, in its infancy, a vast unexplored world filled with new information. You would constantly find new and exciting ideas, groups or sometimes applications that would open you up to new possibilities and ways of working.
I recall when I found all of Kai Krause’s Power Tools documents on a CompuServe forum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The mystery of Watch What Happens</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/watch-what-happens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/watch-what-happens/</guid>
      <description>I am not as educated in music theory or the specifics of music composition as I would like. This often leads me to puzzles for which I don&amp;rsquo;t have the answers and which are, typically, too detailed for me to find answers online. Case in point, the rendition of Watch What Happens that Oscar Peterson plays on the Live At Ronnie Scott&amp;rsquo;s 1974 set.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
