<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apple on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/apple/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apple on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 17:40:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/apple/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Germans gain a cart</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/creating-anagrams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 17:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/creating-anagrams/</guid>
      <description>From time to time I do anagrams. Nothing serious. I certainly don&amp;rsquo;t do it professionally but I have a fondness for making letters jump into new words. I have an odd relationship with words. I like them but I often have difficulty keeping the straight in my head. And my eyes and my brain sometimes disagree on what a series of words actually mean. So it is an odd fascination to have and an even odder skill to practice when you have several disadvantages at work making the process more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Begging for scraps</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/begging-for-scraps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/begging-for-scraps/</guid>
      <description>I am, in a few respects, not the average Mac consumer. I tend to use my hardware until it breaks (I once dropped a Macbook Pro onto a floor and split the case) or it no longer works well for the tasks that I need it. And even then I try to reuse them. The old iMac I used to do Flex (ugh!) and Director programming on is now in the basement running a Plex server for the family and acting as a print server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All the news</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-the-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-the-news/</guid>
      <description>Last month I purchased a Bluetooth speaker to use around the house so I could play music while I worked. We have a very old CD player in the kitchen but the speakers are showing their age and sound rather muffled. It is also not very portable and so a new electronic doodad was purchased. I bought it at Best Buy which is a Canadian electronics chain store. I spent quite a bit of time looking for a locally owned store that sold them but wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to find one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets check the Map!</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/lets-check-the-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/lets-check-the-map/</guid>
      <description>The modern internet is the antithesis of curation. This is, for the most part, the common ground for the problems that haunt large web-sites such as YouTube, Facebook and others. They get so many submissions and at such a high rate that it is humanly impossible to sort them in any manner. Machine learning has been trotted out as a solution to at least the worse types of content being submitted by people but the problems of scale and a lack of human input extend to many services available online, not the least of which are maps.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
