<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alfred on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/alfred/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alfred on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under the CC BY-NC-ND 4.0 license. https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 12:29:10 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/alfred/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create Obsidian Link Workflow</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/createobsidianlink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 12:29:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/createobsidianlink/</guid>
      <description>A while ago, I wrote about an Alfred Workflow to open pages in an Obsidian Vault. It was part of the start of a more robust Workflow to let me store all of my bookmarks in Obsidian instead of my browser. I posted about it but I never put the Workflow on Github as I originally planned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opening Obsidian notes</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/obsidiannotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 21:03:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/obsidiannotes/</guid>
      <description>A while back I decided that the best place for my bookmarks was in Obsidian. They look better there, I can tag then easily and I have also split them into distinct pages. Simple enough but I didn&amp;rsquo;t have an easy way to get the bookmarks into Obsidian from my browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rich CLI .svg Workflow</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/richsvg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 10:22:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/richsvg/</guid>
      <description>Part of the Textual/Rich library ecosystem is a library called Rich CLI. It has a number of features but the one that has me most interested is its ability to export HTML and SVG versions of source code, Markdown and .csv files.
You can use this command line command
1rich -n -g _preflight_all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combined Hugo Workflow</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/hugo-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 11:11:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/hugo-workflow/</guid>
      <description>I seem to have settled on using Hugo as my blogging platform. Since I have started using Alfred, I have put together one or two Workflows to help make it easier to create and edit posts. Those worked well but there were two problems. All of the paths in the scripts were hard-coded and the actions to create or edit content had different scripts for the two content types on my blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Apps - One Action</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/two-apps-one-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 11:42:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/two-apps-one-action/</guid>
      <description>A little while ago I wrote about a Shortcut that I used to lay out images of Scrabble tiles 1 in FreeForm to help solve anagrams. As part of that post I said:
I then looked at doing it in Keyboard Maestro but I couldn’t seem to find a way to iterate over each character in a string.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building an Alfred workflow</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/alfred-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 21:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/alfred-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes the best way to learn how to use a new tool is to just dive in and see what it can do. I am working on a post about various automation tools and apps on the Mac at the moment. And as part of that, the folks at Running with Crayons sent me a key for the Powerpack in Alfred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UTI Problems</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/uti-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 22:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/uti-problems/</guid>
      <description>The underpinnings of an operating system can be mysterious and complex. This typically isn&amp;rsquo;t a problem if the system is working correctly as you will never need to worry yourself with any of those messy parts. When they start to fail you will, unfortunately, need to dig underneath the calm exterior of your OS into the largely text-based underpinnings that make it work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
