<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>All the news</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-the-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-the-news/</guid>
      <description>All the news Last month I purchased a Bluetooth speaker to use around the house so I could play music while I worked. We have a very old CD player in the kitchen but the speakers are showing their age and sound rather muffled. It is also not very portable and so a new electronic doodad was purchased. I bought it at Best Buy which is a Canadian electronics chain store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break a leg</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/break-a-leg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/break-a-leg/</guid>
      <description>Break a leg My grandmother, on my mother&amp;rsquo;s side, passed away due to complications during surgery. It is a pleasing way to say that she was too old and the rigour of the procedure was too much for her system to bear. She was, if I recall correctly, 93 years of age and living with my uncle. They had a small farm in the interior of British Columbia, that my uncle maintained, which they moved to after selling a larger farm in northern BC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game pricing and the yoots</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/game-pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/game-pricing/</guid>
      <description>Game pricing and the yoots Part of getting older is having to realise that times change and that you will invariably not understand what they become. It is difficult to do. You stop being the generation that taste is made for and start becoming that old man who complains about the music playing in the bookstore. So I realise this and I accept it but there are instances when you wonder whether you are right or &amp;ldquo;the kids&amp;rdquo; are and it can be a difficult path to navigate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking languidly</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/breaking-languidly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/breaking-languidly/</guid>
      <description>Breaking languidly The Tower Defence games should have been the first warning.
I truly love TD games, especially Core Defense, and have had since I saw Fieldrunners on the iPad. Fieldrunners was followed by Fieldrunners 2 which was even better than the original and which I have played to completion several times.
I missed playing TD games when they first starting to be come a genre mostly because I didn&amp;rsquo;t really play a lot of Flash games and the games iterated so quickly that it was not a simple task to keep up with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets check the Map!</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/lets-check-the-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/lets-check-the-map/</guid>
      <description>Lets check the Map! The modern internet is the antithesis of curation. This is, for the most part, the common ground for the problems that haunt large web-sites such as YouTube, Facebook and others. They get so many submissions and at such a high rate that it is humanly impossible to sort them in any manner. Machine learning has been trotted out as a solution to at least the worse types of content being submitted by people but the problems of scale and a lack of human input extend to many services available online, not the least of which are maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When you wish upon a...</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/when-you-wish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/when-you-wish/</guid>
      <description>When you wish upon a&amp;hellip; Star light, star bright,
First star I see tonight;
I wish I may, I wish I might
Know if you are a Starlink satellite
2022 has been a year defined by corporations releasing products and services without any thought given to consequences or even such piffling factors as ethics and morality. SpaceX, an Elon Musk company, pushed 100s of satellites into the sky causing havoc for earthbound astronomers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being rich</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/being-rich/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/being-rich/</guid>
      <description>Being rich Being rich isn&amp;rsquo;t a job. Its not as if members of the 1% come home after a long day of being a billionaire and flop into a well-worn La-Z-Boy, pop open a can of a local discount lager and fall asleep watching the evening news. Being rich is a skill though and I think that Elon Musk is at the pinnacle of the craft of being rich.
Now it isn&amp;rsquo;t difficult to be rich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All things will die</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-things-will-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-things-will-die/</guid>
      <description>All things will die The Guardian posted an article today looking at the impact and future of Meta’s Metaverse project. It is not a good read if you are holding Meta stock but I guess nothing really has been for the last few months. What I found most interesting in the article were the comments from Meta vice-president Vishal Shah trying to get his staff and developers to use their own VR software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music on tap</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/music/</guid>
      <description>Music on tap So I would prefer, if possible, to own my music. I have a longterm goal of building a decent sound system and buying some older jazz albums to listen to. Putting an Oscar Peterson album on and listening to it and making the timing of my morning work revolve around having to turn the album over each time it finishes playing.
That said, I recently subscribed to Apple Music and it is almost beyond contemplation how much music I have access to now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Garden</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/secret-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/secret-garden/</guid>
      <description>Secret Garden The internet was, in its infancy, a vast unexplored world filled with new information. You would constantly find new and exciting ideas, groups or sometimes applications that would open you up to new possibilities and ways of working.
I recall when I found all of Kai Krause’s Power Tools documents on a CompuServe forum. Not the plugins for Photoshop but a series of Word files in which he explained a series of mind-bending techniques he used to create complex and wonderful effects in Photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The mystery of Watch What Happens</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/watch-what-happens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/watch-what-happens/</guid>
      <description>The mystery of Watch What Happens I am not as educated in music theory or the specifics of music composition as I would like. This often leads me to puzzles for which I don&amp;rsquo;t have the answers and which are, typically, too detailed for me to find answers online. Case in point, the rendition of Watch What Happens that Oscar Peterson plays on the Live At Ronnie Scott&amp;rsquo;s 1974 set. First though, if you will indulge me, a brief tangent as I explain how I even started listening to this piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing with Markdown</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/writing-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/writing-markdown/</guid>
      <description>Writing with Markdown Some time ago I started doing most of my writing using Markdown. Almost everything I write end up online, either in a blog or website, and so it made sense to use a formatting system that was web-friendly. The more I used it though the more I wanted to use it everywhere. Being able to format you copy as you type, without having to move a mouse or use a menu, allows you to work without having to interrupt your thought process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
