<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 21:29:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building an Alfred workflow</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/alfred-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 21:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/alfred-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes the best way to learn how to use a new tool is to just dive in and see what it can do. I am working on a post about various automation tools and apps on the Mac at the moment. And as part of that, the folks at Running with Crayons sent me a key for the Powerpack in Alfred. Unlike LaunchBar or Raycast you can&amp;rsquo;t access the Workflow automation tools that come with Powerpack without a license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UTI Problems</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/uti-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 22:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/uti-problems/</guid>
      <description>The underpinnings of an operating system can be mysterious and complex. This typically isn&amp;rsquo;t a problem if the system is working correctly as you will never need to worry yourself with any of those messy parts. When they start to fail you will, unfortunately, need to dig underneath the calm exterior of your OS into the largely text-based underpinnings that make it work. It is never pretty.
Our story begins I wanted to do a very simple thing in Alfred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Enshittification of Raycast</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/raycast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 14:34:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/raycast/</guid>
      <description>I am not sure if he came up with the term but, Cory Doctorow has certainly popularised Enshittification as well as providing the a handy list of the steps companies go through as they enshitiffy themselves. I have been thinking of that process a lot this week as I have been looking at various new software releases - Fig, Warp and Raycast 1. These are all attempts to modernise a facet of computing often overlooked (terminals and application launching) as well as adding team and enterprise components to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why we can&#39;t have nice things</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/why-we-cant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 14:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/why-we-cant/</guid>
      <description>You may be familiar with the name Taboola. They are a US-based advertising agency that became infamous for plastering the internet with &amp;ldquo;Recommended&amp;rdquo; links at the end of news articles and online content. You could lose belly fat by not eating one fruit. Or a politician was suggesting you buy gold. Or you would be surprised by how some celebrity looked before they were famous. Perhaps you might be interested in one weird trick?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Files and Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/files-and-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 08:35:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/files-and-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>The last two weeks I have been working, on and off, to solve a problem I had with running a Shortcut in Hazel. I have quite a few rules in Hazel to process files as I download them. One of them attempted to rename a file and then move it. The files had tags in the filename that were separated by brackets. Items like the year of publication, author etc. The number of these tags isn&amp;rsquo;t always the same and so I needed a regular expression to snip all of them from the filename.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Matter CMS</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/front-matter-cms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 22:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/front-matter-cms/</guid>
      <description>A while ago I was talking about possibly using Ulysses as my Markdown writing tool of choice. I tried using it to write a few posts to this blog but I ran into several issues. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into them in detail but just summarize them by saying that Ulysses will edit the content of the YAML front matter in your files in such a way that is contrary to the YAML specifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Germans gain a cart</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/creating-anagrams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 17:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/creating-anagrams/</guid>
      <description>From time to time I do anagrams. Nothing serious. I certainly don&amp;rsquo;t do it professionally but I have a fondness for making letters jump into new words. I have an odd relationship with words. I like them but I often have difficulty keeping the straight in my head. And my eyes and my brain sometimes disagree on what a series of words actually mean. So it is an odd fascination to have and an even odder skill to practice when you have several disadvantages at work making the process more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing is enabling</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/sharing_is/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 15:01:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/sharing_is/</guid>
      <description>There is a very nice JavaScript library available that makes it easy to add a Share to Mastodon link to your website or blog. It is also on GitHub if that is how you roll. The library gives you a significant amount of flexibility to make the button display in a way that works with your site design. It also lets you host the code on your site, which is always a good option to have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poisoned well</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/poisoned_well/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 12:30:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/poisoned_well/</guid>
      <description>People are, rightly, worried about the impact that systems like ChatGPT will have on the veracity of information in general and our ability to find accurate information on search engines such as Google, Bing and Duck Duck Go. I would like to suggest that this is already a problem and that a relentless AI circle-jerk of content referencing will make most of the internet unusable.
Battery disposal Google search pages recently started telling people that it was safe to dispose of their car batteries by throwing them in the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conservative Private Member&#39;s Bill corrections</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/conservative_private_member_bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 14:00:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/conservative_private_member_bill/</guid>
      <description>Conservatives introduce law to indirectly &amp;ldquo;defend&amp;rdquo; the fetus The Conservative Party of Canada announced, on their website, the addition of a Private Member&amp;rsquo;s Bill by MP Cathay Wagantall. The Bill has numerous statistical errors and also appears to be yet another attempt by a Conservative Party MP to push anti-abortion legislation under the guise of trying to stand up to crime.
The announcement OTTAWA, ON — Cathay Wagantall 1, Member of Parliament for Yorkton-Melville, today introduced her private Members’ bill, the Violence Against Pregnant Women Act, in the House of Commons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The frameworks are crazy</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/the-frameworks-are-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 14:35:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/the-frameworks-are-crazy/</guid>
      <description>I had a break from programming for a bit more than a decade. Prior to that I used to build CMS solutions and do multimedia programming in Director 1. One of my favourite things to do was to build automation workflows and development frameworks. When I was working at Bayleaf Software in Vancouver I developed a framework for our ColdFusion coding projects and also build some tools in VTML which was a markup language that the ColdFusion Studio IDE 2 used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are not funny</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/you-are-not-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 15:44:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/you-are-not-funny/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps you have seen it happen online? Someone posts a comment and then appends the phrase &amp;lsquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a joke&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;Humour for the humour impaired&amp;rsquo; or some variant. I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about the people that post some deplorable remark and then try to dissemble their way clear of critique by claiming to be a humorist. Those people are often racists, sexists, bullies or some combination of the three. No, the people I refer to are those who have, in their time online, been misunderstood so often and by so many people that they feel the need to add a qualifier to their comments to underline that they intend it as a joke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Links page</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/creating-a-links-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 14:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/creating-a-links-page/</guid>
      <description>I joke with my friends that a programmer is a person who is a particular type of lazy. They will spend hours or even days on writing code or building a system so they never have to do a task twice. Regardless of the size of the task. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if this is a universal trait but it does describe how I often approach tasks that I know I will repeat again and again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watching Black Panther</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/watching-black-panther/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 08:49:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/watching-black-panther/</guid>
      <description>After a significant wait I was finally able to watch Black Panther: Wakanda Forever. It is a long movie so I had to digest it in two sittings but it was well worth the time.
I will try to avoid discussing specific plot points but if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen the film yet then you may want to wait to read this until later.
I am always impressed by Winston Duke&amp;rsquo;s acting skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Begging for scraps</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/begging-for-scraps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/begging-for-scraps/</guid>
      <description>I am, in a few respects, not the average Mac consumer. I tend to use my hardware until it breaks (I once dropped a Macbook Pro onto a floor and split the case) or it no longer works well for the tasks that I need it. And even then I try to reuse them. The old iMac I used to do Flex (ugh!) and Director programming on is now in the basement running a Plex server for the family and acting as a print server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown writing tools</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/markdown-editors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/markdown-editors/</guid>
      <description>Since starting to write using Markdown it has become, as I have commented, an obsession with me. I currently use Nota to write and organize all of my work and while it is quite good it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have everything that I want. Primarily, it currently doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any Shortcuts or AppleScript support which makes plugging it into an automated workflow trickier than needed. It is also an electron app and I like to find MacOS options when I can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/buildingwithhugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/buildingwithhugo/</guid>
      <description>This site is built using a static site generator called Hugo. Hugo is a command line tool written using the Go language that takes Markdown or HTML pages and builds a website using a theme you specify. The resulting site consists of static HTML pages and so it loads ridiculously quickly and the pages are much smaller than pages built with a CMS.
I am using a theme for the site based on the Poison theme which is itself based on another theme called Hyde.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello new blog</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/hellohugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/hellohugo/</guid>
      <description>If you are here reading this post then you have found my blog in its new home. I was, until yesterday, using Wordpress as a hosting service but have moved all of my recent writing to this new location. There are two primary reasons for this.
I might still be using Wordpress if I hadn’t made the mistake of viewing the site without my ad blocker and saw these:
At the bottom of every blog post were a series of ads from companies such as Outbrain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All the news</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-the-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-the-news/</guid>
      <description>Last month I purchased a Bluetooth speaker to use around the house so I could play music while I worked. We have a very old CD player in the kitchen but the speakers are showing their age and sound rather muffled. It is also not very portable and so a new electronic doodad was purchased. I bought it at Best Buy which is a Canadian electronics chain store. I spent quite a bit of time looking for a locally owned store that sold them but wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to find one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break a leg</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/break-a-leg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/break-a-leg/</guid>
      <description>My grandmother, on my mother&amp;rsquo;s side, passed away due to complications during surgery. It is a pleasing way to say that she was too old and the rigour of the procedure was too much for her system to bear. She was, if I recall correctly, 93 years of age and living with my uncle. They had a small farm in the interior of British Columbia, that my uncle maintained, which they moved to after selling a larger farm in northern BC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game pricing</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/game-pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/game-pricing/</guid>
      <description>Part of getting older is having to realise that times change and that you will invariably not understand what they become. It is difficult to do. You stop being the generation that taste is made for and start becoming that old man who complains about the music playing in the bookstore. So I realise this and I accept it but there are instances when you wonder whether you are right or &amp;ldquo;the kids&amp;rdquo; are and it can be a difficult path to navigate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking languidly</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/breaking-languidly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/breaking-languidly/</guid>
      <description>The Tower Defence games should have been the first warning.
I truly love TD games, especially Core Defense, and have had since I saw Fieldrunners on the iPad. Fieldrunners was followed by Fieldrunners 2 which was even better than the original and which I have played to completion several times.
I missed playing TD games when they first starting to be come a genre mostly because I didn&amp;rsquo;t really play a lot of Flash games and the games iterated so quickly that it was not a simple task to keep up with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets check the Map!</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/lets-check-the-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/lets-check-the-map/</guid>
      <description>The modern internet is the antithesis of curation. This is, for the most part, the common ground for the problems that haunt large web-sites such as YouTube, Facebook and others. They get so many submissions and at such a high rate that it is humanly impossible to sort them in any manner. Machine learning has been trotted out as a solution to at least the worse types of content being submitted by people but the problems of scale and a lack of human input extend to many services available online, not the least of which are maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When you wish upon a...</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/when-you-wish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/when-you-wish/</guid>
      <description>Star light, star bright,
First star I see tonight;
I wish I may, I wish I might
Know if you are a Starlink satellite
2022 has been a year defined by corporations releasing products and services without any thought given to consequences or even such piffling factors as ethics and morality. SpaceX, an Elon Musk company, pushed 100s of satellites into the sky causing havoc for earthbound astronomers. The company has plans for a total of 2700 low-earth orbit satellites which is slightly more than 50% of the existing number of objects in low-earth orbit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being rich</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/being-rich/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/being-rich/</guid>
      <description>Being rich isn&amp;rsquo;t a job. Its not as if members of the 1% come home after a long day of being a billionaire and flop into a well-worn La-Z-Boy, pop open a can of a local discount lager and fall asleep watching the evening news. Being rich is a skill though and I think that Elon Musk is at the pinnacle of the craft of being rich.
Now it isn&amp;rsquo;t difficult to be rich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All things will die</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-things-will-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-things-will-die/</guid>
      <description>The Guardian posted an article today looking at the impact and future of Meta’s Metaverse project. It is not a good read if you are holding Meta stock but I guess nothing really has been for the last few months. What I found most interesting in the article were the comments from Meta vice-president Vishal Shah trying to get his staff and developers to use their own VR software.
“If we don’t love it, how can we expect our users to love it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music on tap</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/music/</guid>
      <description>So I would prefer, if possible, to own my music. I have a longterm goal of building a decent sound system and buying some older jazz albums to listen to. Putting an Oscar Peterson album on and listening to it and making the timing of my morning work revolve around having to turn the album over each time it finishes playing.
That said, I recently subscribed to Apple Music and it is almost beyond contemplation how much music I have access to now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Garden</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/secret-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/secret-garden/</guid>
      <description>The internet was, in its infancy, a vast unexplored world filled with new information. You would constantly find new and exciting ideas, groups or sometimes applications that would open you up to new possibilities and ways of working.
I recall when I found all of Kai Krause’s Power Tools documents on a CompuServe forum. Not the plugins for Photoshop but a series of Word files in which he explained a series of mind-bending techniques he used to create complex and wonderful effects in Photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The mystery of Watch What Happens</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/watch-what-happens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/watch-what-happens/</guid>
      <description>I am not as educated in music theory or the specifics of music composition as I would like. This often leads me to puzzles for which I don&amp;rsquo;t have the answers and which are, typically, too detailed for me to find answers online. Case in point, the rendition of Watch What Happens that Oscar Peterson plays on the Live At Ronnie Scott&amp;rsquo;s 1974 set. First though, if you will indulge me, a brief tangent as I explain how I even started listening to this piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing with Markdown</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/writing-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/writing-markdown/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago I started doing most of my writing using Markdown. Almost everything I write end up online, either in a blog or website, and so it made sense to use a formatting system that was web-friendly. The more I used it though the more I wanted to use it everywhere. Being able to format you copy as you type, without having to move a mouse or use a menu, allows you to work without having to interrupt your thought process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
