<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Interesting Links #1</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/interesting-links-02012023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/interesting-links-02012023/</guid>
      <description>This is just something that I am trying out. Mostly to be able to post comments about interesting articles but also to see what it is that I need to do to create a workflow to support doing this type of post.
Today&amp;rsquo;s links How Hollywood is breaking the VFX industry
This was posted by Kieron Gillen on Mastodon. It is a very interesting read for many reasons. This has been a problem in the VFX industry for close to 20 years and seems to be getting worse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Begging for scraps</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/begging-for-scraps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/begging-for-scraps/</guid>
      <description>I am, in a few respects, not the average Mac consumer. I tend to use my hardware until it breaks (I once dropped a Macbook Pro onto a floor and split the case) or it no longer works well for the tasks that I need it. And even then I try to reuse them. The old iMac I used to do Flex (ugh!) and Director programming on is now in the basement running a Plex server for the family and acting as a print server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown writing tools</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/markdown-editors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/markdown-editors/</guid>
      <description>Since starting to write using Markdown it has become, as I have commented, an obsession with me. I currently use Nota to write and organize all of my work and while it is quite good it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have everything that I want. Primarily, it currently doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any Shortcuts or AppleScript support which makes plugging it into an automated workflow trickier than needed. It is also an electron app and I like to find MacOS options when I can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/buildingwithhugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/buildingwithhugo/</guid>
      <description>This site is built using a static site generator called Hugo. Hugo is a command line tool written using the Go language that takes Markdown or HTML pages and builds a website using a theme you specify. The resulting site consists of static HTML pages and so it loads ridiculously quickly and the pages are much smaller than pages built with a CMS.
I am using a theme for the site based on the Poison theme which is itself based on another theme called Hyde.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello new blog</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/hellohugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/hellohugo/</guid>
      <description>If you are here reading this post then you have found my blog in its new home. I was, until yesterday, using Wordpress as a hosting service but have moved all of my recent writing to this new location. There are two primary reasons for this.
I might still be using Wordpress if I hadn’t made the mistake of viewing the site without my ad blocker and saw these:
At the bottom of every blog post were a series of ads from companies such as Outbrain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All the news</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-the-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-the-news/</guid>
      <description>Last month I purchased a Bluetooth speaker to use around the house so I could play music while I worked. We have a very old CD player in the kitchen but the speakers are showing their age and sound rather muffled. It is also not very portable and so a new electronic doodad was purchased. I bought it at Best Buy which is a Canadian electronics chain store. I spent quite a bit of time looking for a locally owned store that sold them but wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to find one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break a leg</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/break-a-leg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/break-a-leg/</guid>
      <description>My grandmother, on my mother&amp;rsquo;s side, passed away due to complications during surgery. It is a pleasing way to say that she was too old and the rigour of the procedure was too much for her system to bear. She was, if I recall correctly, 93 years of age and living with my uncle. They had a small farm in the interior of British Columbia, that my uncle maintained, which they moved to after selling a larger farm in northern BC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game pricing</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/game-pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/game-pricing/</guid>
      <description>Part of getting older is having to realise that times change and that you will invariably not understand what they become. It is difficult to do. You stop being the generation that taste is made for and start becoming that old man who complains about the music playing in the bookstore. So I realise this and I accept it but there are instances when you wonder whether you are right or &amp;ldquo;the kids&amp;rdquo; are and it can be a difficult path to navigate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking languidly</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/breaking-languidly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/breaking-languidly/</guid>
      <description>The Tower Defence games should have been the first warning.
I truly love TD games, especially Core Defense, and have had since I saw Fieldrunners on the iPad. Fieldrunners was followed by Fieldrunners 2 which was even better than the original and which I have played to completion several times.
I missed playing TD games when they first starting to be come a genre mostly because I didn&amp;rsquo;t really play a lot of Flash games and the games iterated so quickly that it was not a simple task to keep up with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets check the Map!</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/lets-check-the-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/lets-check-the-map/</guid>
      <description>The modern internet is the antithesis of curation. This is, for the most part, the common ground for the problems that haunt large web-sites such as YouTube, Facebook and others. They get so many submissions and at such a high rate that it is humanly impossible to sort them in any manner. Machine learning has been trotted out as a solution to at least the worse types of content being submitted by people but the problems of scale and a lack of human input extend to many services available online, not the least of which are maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When you wish upon a...</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/when-you-wish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/when-you-wish/</guid>
      <description>Star light, star bright,
First star I see tonight;
I wish I may, I wish I might
Know if you are a Starlink satellite
2022 has been a year defined by corporations releasing products and services without any thought given to consequences or even such piffling factors as ethics and morality. SpaceX, an Elon Musk company, pushed 100s of satellites into the sky causing havoc for earthbound astronomers. The company has plans for a total of 2700 low-earth orbit satellites which is slightly more than 50% of the existing number of objects in low-earth orbit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being rich</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/being-rich/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/being-rich/</guid>
      <description>Being rich isn&amp;rsquo;t a job. Its not as if members of the 1% come home after a long day of being a billionaire and flop into a well-worn La-Z-Boy, pop open a can of a local discount lager and fall asleep watching the evening news. Being rich is a skill though and I think that Elon Musk is at the pinnacle of the craft of being rich.
Now it isn&amp;rsquo;t difficult to be rich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All things will die</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-things-will-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/all-things-will-die/</guid>
      <description>The Guardian posted an article today looking at the impact and future of Meta’s Metaverse project. It is not a good read if you are holding Meta stock but I guess nothing really has been for the last few months. What I found most interesting in the article were the comments from Meta vice-president Vishal Shah trying to get his staff and developers to use their own VR software.
“If we don’t love it, how can we expect our users to love it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music on tap</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/music/</guid>
      <description>So I would prefer, if possible, to own my music. I have a longterm goal of building a decent sound system and buying some older jazz albums to listen to. Putting an Oscar Peterson album on and listening to it and making the timing of my morning work revolve around having to turn the album over each time it finishes playing.
That said, I recently subscribed to Apple Music and it is almost beyond contemplation how much music I have access to now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Garden</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/secret-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/secret-garden/</guid>
      <description>The internet was, in its infancy, a vast unexplored world filled with new information. You would constantly find new and exciting ideas, groups or sometimes applications that would open you up to new possibilities and ways of working.
I recall when I found all of Kai Krause’s Power Tools documents on a CompuServe forum. Not the plugins for Photoshop but a series of Word files in which he explained a series of mind-bending techniques he used to create complex and wonderful effects in Photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The mystery of Watch What Happens</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/watch-what-happens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/watch-what-happens/</guid>
      <description>I am not as educated in music theory or the specifics of music composition as I would like. This often leads me to puzzles for which I don&amp;rsquo;t have the answers and which are, typically, too detailed for me to find answers online. Case in point, the rendition of Watch What Happens that Oscar Peterson plays on the Live At Ronnie Scott&amp;rsquo;s 1974 set. First though, if you will indulge me, a brief tangent as I explain how I even started listening to this piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing with Markdown</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/writing-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/writing-markdown/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago I started doing most of my writing using Markdown. Almost everything I write end up online, either in a blog or website, and so it made sense to use a formatting system that was web-friendly. The more I used it though the more I wanted to use it everywhere. Being able to format you copy as you type, without having to move a mouse or use a menu, allows you to work without having to interrupt your thought process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
