<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MacOS on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/macos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MacOS on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under the CC BY-NC-ND 4.0 license. https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 09:31:20 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/macos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Artisanal software</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/artisinalsoftware/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 09:31:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/artisinalsoftware/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t listen to many podcasts. My interests, even when taking my ADHD medication, tend to flit and bounce with the trajectory of a dust mote in a wind funnel. And so I haven&amp;rsquo;t really been interested in many topics long enough to develop a habit of listening to podcasts about them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changes are afoot</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/changesafoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 10:07:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/changesafoot/</guid>
      <description>For the last year or so I have been working on a MacBook Air. This was fine when all I was doing was writing but as I am doing coding I was finding the small screen size to be limiting. So yesterday I went our and bought a 24&amp;quot; monitor, a stand for the MacBook and an Anker USB C port to allow the MacBook to drive the monitor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inkscape command line on the Mac</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/inskcapemac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 08:37:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/inskcapemac/</guid>
      <description>I have been testing out the Inskscape command line tool for the last few days and thought I would share a small tip.
On the Mac the command line tools are accessed via an executable inside the Inskscape .app package. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t load any binaries so you have to call it with the path to the Inkscape application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building an Alfred workflow</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/alfred-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 21:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/alfred-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes the best way to learn how to use a new tool is to just dive in and see what it can do. I am working on a post about various automation tools and apps on the Mac at the moment. And as part of that, the folks at Running with Crayons sent me a key for the Powerpack in Alfred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Files and Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/files-and-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 08:35:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/files-and-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>The last two weeks I have been working, on and off, to solve a problem I had with running a Shortcut in Hazel. I have quite a few rules in Hazel to process files as I download them. One of them attempted to rename a file and then move it. The files had tags in the filename that were separated by brackets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown writing tools</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/markdown-editors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 18:37:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/markdown-editors/</guid>
      <description>Since starting to write using Markdown it has become, as I have commented, an obsession with me. I currently use Nota to write and organize all of my work and while it is quite good it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have everything that I want. Primarily, it currently doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any Shortcuts or AppleScript support which makes plugging it into an automated workflow trickier than needed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
