<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asshats on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/asshats/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Asshats on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 15:44:39 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/asshats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Are not funny</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/you-are-not-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 15:44:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/you-are-not-funny/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps you have seen it happen online? Someone posts a comment and then appends the phrase &amp;lsquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a joke&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;Humour for the humour impaired&amp;rsquo; or some variant. I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about the people that post some deplorable remark and then try to dissemble their way clear of critique by claiming to be a humorist. Those people are often racists, sexists, bullies or some combination of the three. No, the people I refer to are those who have, in their time online, been misunderstood so often and by so many people that they feel the need to add a qualifier to their comments to underline that they intend it as a joke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being rich</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/being-rich/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/being-rich/</guid>
      <description>Being rich isn&amp;rsquo;t a job. Its not as if members of the 1% come home after a long day of being a billionaire and flop into a well-worn La-Z-Boy, pop open a can of a local discount lager and fall asleep watching the evening news. Being rich is a skill though and I think that Elon Musk is at the pinnacle of the craft of being rich.
Now it isn&amp;rsquo;t difficult to be rich.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
