<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nota on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/nota/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nota on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under the CC BY-NC-ND 4.0 license. https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 15:59:41 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/nota/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Making Footnotes</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/making-footnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 15:59:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/making-footnotes/</guid>
      <description>I like footnotes 1. Part of the blame for this has to lay with Terry Pratchett and his Discworld novels. Pratchett had a propensity for adding footnotes to his stories to, occasionally, add details to a line but, most often, to continue a joke or to sometimes ramble on for a half page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown writing tools</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/markdown-editors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 18:37:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/markdown-editors/</guid>
      <description>Since starting to write using Markdown it has become, as I have commented, an obsession with me. I currently use Nota to write and organize all of my work and while it is quite good it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have everything that I want. Primarily, it currently doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any Shortcuts or AppleScript support which makes plugging it into an automated workflow trickier than needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing with Markdown</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/writing-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/writing-markdown/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago I started doing most of my writing using Markdown. Almost everything I write end up online, either in a blog or website, and so it made sense to use a formatting system that was web-friendly. The more I used it though the more I wanted to use it everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
