<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Victor on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/victor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Victor on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under the CC BY-NC-ND 4.0 license. https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:33:50 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/victor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Preflight rework</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/preflightrework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:33:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/preflightrework/</guid>
      <description>I did a fair bit of work on my preflight app/command last night. Primarily it was to add an argument to the command line to allow the user to add config data to the code so it knows where the user&amp;rsquo;s Hugo installation is.
I was reading through the Python Docs for argparse options as I was trying to make sure that the code would display help even if it was missing configuration data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Victor update</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/victorupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 17:48:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/victorupdate/</guid>
      <description>The last few days have been taken up with work on my Textual app - Victor. I mentioned it in my last post and I have been typing away getting new features included. This is how the app currently looks.
The app will read in the path to your local Hugo install and then read through the content directory looking for Markdown files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subclassing with PyCharm</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/pycharm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 08:03:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/pycharm/</guid>
      <description>Today has been a day filled with writing and rewriting code. For the last few days I have bashing around in a command line UI system called Textual. It is a Python based Rapid Application Development framework that lets you build TUI applications. Terminal User Interface. If it isn&amp;rsquo;t the geekiest thing I have ever done I don&amp;rsquo;t know what is.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
