<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Markdown on What is wrong with your dog?</title>
    <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/markdown/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Markdown on What is wrong with your dog?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under the CC BY-NC-ND 4.0 license. https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 22:59:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/tags/markdown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UTI Problems</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/uti-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 22:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/uti-problems/</guid>
      <description>The underpinnings of an operating system can be mysterious and complex. This typically isn&amp;rsquo;t a problem if the system is working correctly as you will never need to worry yourself with any of those messy parts. When they start to fail you will, unfortunately, need to dig underneath the calm exterior of your OS into the largely text-based underpinnings that make it work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Matter CMS</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/front-matter-cms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 12:26:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/front-matter-cms/</guid>
      <description>A while ago I was talking about possibly using Ulysses as my Markdown writing tool of choice. I tried using it to write a few posts to this blog but I ran into several issues. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into them in detail but just summarize them by saying that Ulysses will edit the content of the YAML front matter in your files in such a way that is contrary to the YAML specifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown writing tools</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/markdown-editors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 18:37:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/markdown-editors/</guid>
      <description>Since starting to write using Markdown it has become, as I have commented, an obsession with me. I currently use Nota to write and organize all of my work and while it is quite good it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have everything that I want. Primarily, it currently doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any Shortcuts or AppleScript support which makes plugging it into an automated workflow trickier than needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/buildingwithhugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 15:58:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/buildingwithhugo/</guid>
      <description>This site is built using a static site generator called Hugo. Hugo is a command line tool written using the Go language that takes Markdown or HTML pages and builds a website using a theme you specify. The resulting site consists of static HTML pages and so it loads ridiculously quickly and the pages are much smaller than pages built with a CMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing with Markdown</title>
      <link>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/writing-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whatiswrongwithyourdog.netlify.app/posts/writing-markdown/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago I started doing most of my writing using Markdown. Almost everything I write end up online, either in a blog or website, and so it made sense to use a formatting system that was web-friendly. The more I used it though the more I wanted to use it everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
